[
    {
        "numb": 1,
        "question": " Hyperlinks cannot be ? ",
        "answer": " All can be hyperlinks",
        "options": [
            "Special shapes like stars and banners",
            "Drawing objects like rectangles ovals",
            "Pictures",
            "All can be hyperlinks"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 2,
        "question": "You can add an image to a template by clicking the insert picture from file button on the …. Toolbar. ?",
        "answer": "Picture",
        "options": [
            "Standard",
            "Formatting",
            "Drawing",
            "Picture"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 3,
        "question": " To drag a selected range of data to another worksheet in the same workbook, use the ?",
        "answer": "interface",
        "options": [
            "application",
            "program",
            "server",
            "interface"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 4,
        "question": "  You can open the Sort dialog box by choosing Sort from the ….. Menu?",
        "answer": "Data ",
        "options": [
            "View",
            "Format",
            "Data ",
            "Tools"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 5,
        "question": " When you print preview a worksheet?",
        "answer": "a, b and c",
        "options": [
            "The entire worksheet is displayed",
            "The selected range is displayed",
            "The active portion of the worksheet is displayed ",
            "a, b and c"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 6,
        "question": "When working in the page break preview, you can",
        "answer": "All of above",
        "options": [
            "View exactly where each page break occurs ",
            "Add or remove page breaks",
            "Change the print area",
            "All of above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 7,
        "question": "________ is an embedded operating system resides on a ROM chip on a mobile device or consumer electronic device?",
        "answer": "Mobile OS",
        "options": [
            "Stand-alone OS",
            "Server OS",
            "Mobile OS",
            "Free OS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 8,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a valid Zoom percentage in Excel? ",
        "answer": "500",
        "options": [
            "10",
            "100",
            "300",
            "500"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 9,
        "question": "The spelling tool is placed on ______ toolbar ?",
        "answer": "Standard",
        "options": [
            "Standard",
            "Formatting",
            "Drawing",
            "Reviewing "
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 10,
        "question": "Formatting a cell in Number format you can’t set?",
        "answer": "Negative numbers",
        "options": [
            "Decimal Places ",
            "Use 1000 separator",
            "Negative numbers ",
            "Currency Symbol"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 11,
        "question": " What is entered by the function =today()?",
        "answer": "All of above ",
        "options": [
            "The date value for the day according to system clock",
            "The time value according to system clock ",
            "Today’s date as Text format",
            "All of above "
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 12,
        "question": "Formatting a cell in Currency, you can specify",
        "answer": "Both of above",
        "options": [
            "Decimal Places ",
            "Currency Symbol ",
            "Both of above",
            "None of above."
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 13,
        "question": "Icons, menus and windows are part of:",
        "answer": "Graphical user interface",
        "options": [
            "Graphics or games packages",
            "System security",
            "Applications and user files",
            "Graphical user interface"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 14,
        "question": "The following is not a part of GUI:",
        "answer": "command prompt",
        "options": [
            "scroll bar",
            "command prompt",
            "radio button",
            "text box"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 15,
        "question": " Which function will you use to enter current time in a woksheet cell? .",
        "answer": "=today()",
        "options": [
            "=today()",
            "=now() ",
            "=time()",
            "=currentTime()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 16,
        "question": "Merge cells option can be applied from",
        "answer": "Format Cells dialog box Alignment Tab",
        "options": [
            "Format Cells dialog box Alignment Tab",
            "Formatting toolbar",
            "Both of above",
            "None of above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 17,
        "question": " Which of the following format you can decide to apply or not in AutoFormat dialog box? ",
        "answer": "All of above",
        "options": [
            "Number format",
            "Border format ",
            "Font format",
            "All of above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 18,
        "question": " How can you remove borders applied in cells?",
        "answer": "Both of above",
        "options": [
            "Choose None on Border tab of Format cells",
            "Open the list on Border tool in Formatting toolbar then choose first tool (no border) ",
            "Both of above",
            "None of above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 19,
        "question": " ou can set Page Border in Excel from?",
        "answer": "You can not set page border in Excel ",
        "options": [
            "From Border tab in Format Cells dialog box",
            "From Border tool in Formatting toolbar  ",
            "From Line Style tool in Drawing toolbar",
            "You can not set page border in Excel "
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 20,
        "question": "You can check the conditions against __________ when applying conditional formatting ?",
        "answer": "Both of above",
        "options": [
            "Cell value",
            "Formula",
            "Both of above",
            "None of above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 21,
        "question": " Each excel file is a workbook that contains different sheets. Which of the following can not be a sheet in workbook? ",
        "answer": "data sheet",
        "options": [
            "work sheet",
            "chart sheet",
            "module sheet",
            "data sheet"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 22,
        "question": "When a range is selected, how can you activate the previous cell?",
        "answer": "None of above",
        "options": [
            "Press the Alt key",
            "Press Tab",
            "Press Enter",
            "None of above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 23,
        "question": "Which of the following formulas will Excel Not be able to calculate?",
        "answer": " =SUM(Sales)-A3",
        "options": [
            "=SUM(Sales)-A3",
            "=SUM(A1:A5)*.5 ",
            "=SUM(A1:A5)/(10-10) ",
            "=SUM(A1:A5)-10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 24,
        "question": " To drag a selected range of data to another worksheet in the same workbook, use the",
        "answer": "Ctrl key ",
        "options": [
            "Ctrl key ",
            "Shift key",
            "Alt key",
            "Tab key"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 25,
        "question": "  Hyperlinks can be",
        "answer": " All of above",
        "options": [
            "Text",
            "Drawing objects",
            "Pictures",
            "All of above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 26,
        "question": "To activate the previous cell in a pre-selected range, press",
        "answer": "None of the above",
        "options": [
            "the Alt key",
            "The Tab key",
            "The Enter key",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 27,
        "question": "Which button do you click to add up a series of numbers?",
        "answer": "The auto sum button",
        "options": [
            "The Formula button",
            "The auto sum button ",
            "The quicktotal button",
            "The total button"
        ]
    }
]